for your business, this is exact video
for you. And it's very true. You become
richer when you niche down. But
sometimes it can get very overwhelming.
There are so many options and it feels
like you are losing out on money by
working with one person. But that's not
the case. You make more money when you
work with one person because you're an
expert in that field and you can command
expert prices. The reason why you go to
a optician for an eye problem because
it's an expert with the eyes. You won't
go to a general doctor to fix an eye
issue. And that's exactly how your
clients view businesses, they want to
work with expert, people that understand
their problem so well. I've done it so
many times, not for every other person.
It makes communication even easier
because whatever they are saying to you,
whatever problem they have, you have
seen it so many times and you
communicate better. Also, your content
is much much better. You know how to
make the right content for your
audience. It's just so much better.
However, it can get very overwhelming
and daunting because if you choose the
wrong niche, you will set you back. When
I started my business, I was working
with realtors and it was so difficult
for me to get a client. It took me about
8 months to get a client for my
business. I make websites probably make
website or do gra and it was one of the
hardest of my life. I would explain to
you exactly what you have to do the
criteras you have to you know look at
look out for for you choose a niche and
yeah going to be a very valack video and
stick around. Now
there are so many reasons why you choose
a niche because when you work with one
niche you know where your clients are
unlike when you work with everybody. It
seems like you're working with everybody
you are losing out but it's not the case
because when you work with one niche you
know where they are. You know what to
say to them. You know any problem that
they facing is so much easier for you to
stand out than someone that is working
with every other person. But there are
some criterias you have to look forward
to or look at before you choose a niche.
And I will show you that in this video.
First of all, how much does one client
mean to them? Very, very important. You
could, if I work with someone that is in
private aviation or someone that sells
food, one client for someone that is in
private aviation is so much money for
them. One client for someone that sells
food, it's not really a lot because if
you help this person, let's say you help
them with a website or you help them
with their marketing and you help them
get one client, that's for the person
that does private aviation, one client
could mean about $20,000
for that person. Yeah. And for someone
that sells food, one client could be
like $100. And it doesn't make sense
because you have putting so much effort.
It's the same effort for both of them.
either you run ads for them, you make
website is there's no much different. So
whatever service you're offering to
them, the value you are giving them or
they're getting back is not a lot. You
have to do a lot more for them to break
even on whatever they invest in your
business. Even if you charge like
$2,000, let's say you run ads for
clients and you charge about $2,000 a
month for someone that is in private
aviation, that means that for you to get
for them to get their money back, you
have to bring just one client for them
and they tripled or quadrupled their
money they invested in you. Or someone
that sells full for $100. For them to
get their money back, you have to bring
them about 20 client. That's getting
their money back before even seeing
profit or you know gain in whatever they
invested. It makes so much sense for you
to choose someone that you know is
making so much money and someone that
one client is not a lot of money to
them. You have to work more and it just
doesn't make a lot of sense. And that's
why I chose real estate. Real estate
they make a lot of money from them. But
there's one other thing you have to look
forward to or look at is that how easy
is it to reach out to them. You know, as
much as private aviation is very
lucrative, it's very hard for you to
call the owner of a private jet. They
are mostly billionaires. They have so
much money and you can't just go on
Google and find them and call them. You
can go on Google and find someone that
has a restaurant and call and reach out
to them. It's easy to reach out to them.
But for someone that is a billionaire is
very difficult. You have to choose a
industry that it's kind of easier for
you to reach out to the owner. You can
just call them, text them or send an
email. But for priority aviation, it can
be very difficult for you to reach as
the owner because the owners are the
decision makers, people that are the
receptionist or the staff. They can't
really decide any thing for the company.
It makes no sense trying to pitch them
or reach out to them. Now also, how
saturated is the market? This is the
problem I face in real estate because in
real estate, one client for a realtor is
about like 10k in commission most times.
and you can easily call them but because
you can easily call them there are so
many people that are trying to work with
them so they have gotten so many offers
so many um DMs or outreach and they are
fatigued from whatever offer it's very
hard for them to stand out I sound most
times I sound like the next person like
the next person to have reached out to
them before and they some of them have
tried it they didn't get any success or
they have friends that before and they
never got any success from whatever
sales I'm offering so this was a very
big issue for me if you look at my
screen here. I was sending so many code
DMs at one point in my career. Let me
let me share here. Right here. I was
sending so many code DMs and it was very
hard for me to stand out. There was one
message I got a rejection. It was like,
"Oh no, this is B." He said, "No thanks
though. No thanks. I appreciate the
page. Definitely one of the cleaner one
that comes in my inbox. That means it
gets a lot of this DM or you know from
people that are trying to help me solve
that problem." So real estate was a
no-go area for me. I was very stubborn
and I chose it and I stuck with it. But
I got one client for 8 months and I like
nah I can keep on doing this. Now these
are the most important criteria for
choosing niche. If you have these
criterias dialed in, it's easier for you
to make a choice. Now even if you have
your niche, an offer is very very
important because a lot of times you
have the great the perfect niche but
your offer does not resonate to them.
You're not giving them what they care
about. more you are saying what you care
about and it's very hard for them to
really believe or be incentivized to
work on your whatever you're offering
them. Your offer has to something that
they really care about and they want for
their business. If you can lock in this
and you have a great offer, a great
niche and a great offer, it's easier for
you to get responses from client that
are willing to work with you. So niches
are very very tricky sometime. But when
you have the perfect niche, there's not
really a perfect niche to be honest.
Sometimes you have to just stick with it
for a long time. Once you have a niche
that is easier for you to break into,
you have a great offer, easier for you
to get clients. This is exactly how I
would go about choosing a niche for my
industry. So, if you want to see more of
this or you want to have a one-on-one
call with me, there's a link below. You
can join my private Discord where we
help people with getting client and, you
know, getting more business for themsel.
And yeah, you can have a oneonone call
with I can mentor you on that. All
right. Bye.
[Music]